SHUBHAM KANSE

Pune, Maharashtra

1 7066337272

✓ <u>shubhamkanse7272@gmail.com</u>

in LinkedIn

GitHub

PROFILE

Passionate frontend developer with a total of 2 years in frontend development, including 1.5 years of dedicated experience in Vue.js, React.js and 7 months of internship exposure. Aspiring to become a full stack developer with a focus on the MERN stack. Looking for challenging and responsible opportunity to explore strengths and potential in a professional organization.

SKILLS

Proficient in HTML, JavaScript, Vue js, React js

Familiar with TypeScript, CSS, Git, MySQL, C

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Enovate-IT | Front End Developer

Jun 2022 - Nov 2023

I worked on an educational-based project with primarily three modules, one utilizing Vue.js, and the other two using React.js. My responsibilities included CR development, bug fixes, and enhancement of these modules.

Acropolis Systems | Intern

Jan 2021 - Jul 2021

As an intern at Acropolis, I played a significant role in web development as part of the Smart Traffic Control System project, which encompassed Python, deep learning, and machine learning technologies.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Application

Aug, 2020 - May, 2022

Indira college of engineering and management - CGPA - 8.93

Bachelor of Computer Application

Jul, 2017 - Jun, 2020

Brihan Maharashtra College of Commerce - CGPA - 7.28

PROFESSIONAL PROJECT

Catapult

Led development of an Educational Management System with multiple user roles (students, teachers, parents, institute admin). Three modules were implemented, with the primary one using Vue.js and the others using React.js. Admins can create/schedule tests for students for specific centers or batches, manage or add users, check results of students and broadcast messages. Teachers approve tests, while students can attempt online tests, create self tests for practice, view results, try practice sessions, and download report cards.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

uHost

uHost is a dynamic front-end website designed to provide top-notch hosting services. Developed using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, this project showcases my expertise in front-end development and user experience design.

Tic Tac Toe Game

The Tic Tac Toe game is a fun and interactive web application developed using React.js. It allows two players to engage in a classic game of Tic Tac Toe while also providing the option to customize their names before starting.

CERTIFICATIONS

CSS - The Complete Guide 2024 | Udemy

PROFILE LINKS

• <u>GitHub</u> • <u>LinkedIn</u>

• Leetcode

• Portfolio